Dare to dream your life.
Phoebe in Wonderland is a drama film directed by Daniel Barnz.
The fantastical tale of a little girl who won't - or can't - follow the rules.
Confounded by her clashes with the rule-obsessed world around her, Phoebe seeks enlightenment from her unconventional
drama teacher, even as her brilliant but anguished mother looks to Phoebe herself for inspiration.
Phoebe Lichten, played by Elle Fanning.
Hillary Lichten, played by Felicity Huffman.
Miss Dodger, played by Patricia Clarkson.
Peter Lichten, played by Bill Pullman.
Principal Davis, played by Campbell Scott.
Jamie, played by Ian Colletti.
Phoebe in Wonderland is a 2008 American drama film
written and directed by Daniel Barnz.
It stars Felicity Huffman, Patricia Clarkson,  Elle Fanning (in her
first leading role), Campbell Scott, and Bill Pullman.
It was screened in the Dramatic Competition at the Sundance Film
Festival and the RiverRun International Film Festival in 2008.
The film received a limited theatrical release on March 6,
2009, it received mixed reviews by the critics.
The film explores themes of daughter, bedroom, inspiration, teacher, misfit.
The tone is emotional.